<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[DesignKorps]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[DesignKorps]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/designkorps/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 15:25:28 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/designkorps/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Grand designs]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Grand designs</h1><p>An identity that perfectly captures the ethos of a company builds equity in the brand and projects a differentiated image. When the identity is unique and relevant, it helps make a positive first impression and gets the conversation off to a good start. By contrast, an unattractive or outdated corporate identity makes these goals harder and more expensive to accomplish. I've added several examples of strong clean corporate identity that I executed over the past several years.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/designkorps/grand-designs/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6e10235f-e9f2-4aa4-8679-0a60f52d2982</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 15:24:20 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identify Yourself]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Identify Yourself</h1><p>My name is Carl McDonnell and I'm a Dublin, Ireland-based graphic designer. I have extensive experience providing design solutions for dozens of clients over two decades. My client base covers many business sectors, including publishing, banking, law, FMCG, healthcare, property management, construction, IT, e-learning, education, photography, newspapers and many more.

I'm a multi-platform designer, comfortable with both PC and Mac, but it would be fair to say the vast majority of my work is produced on Mac (the first commercial design computer I used was a Mac Plus, so that gives you a idea of timescale). I love playing with software and besides the industry staples (InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator) I use Dreamweaver, Flash, AfterEffects, Keynote, iBooks author, Resolume. Occasionally on-site, I still need to go back to the good old days of Quark Xpress and (gasp!) Freehand, but those occasions are rare now. I'd love more time to use 3D software but I've dabbled in it for over 10 years, using 'old-school' software such as infini-D, Bryce, but have used Maya and 3D Max several times.

Anyway, this site is basically a project overview of my work over the past few years, with a few 'oldies' thrown in for good measure. I hope you see something you like. Feel free to comment or contact me with any suggestions, criticisms or queries. Enjoy.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/designkorps/identify-yourself/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">231a671a-b326-41e8-a709-1dfcaa6d64a7</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 13:30:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Grace Under Pressure]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Grace Under Pressure</h1><h2>Performance graphics that add a new dimension to live shows</h2></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/designkorps/grace-under-pressure/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">92290727-4ddb-40ff-a4f5-f828db2f43a9</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 15:17:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>